milasandovalsantana@gmail.com 754-261-7176

Tamarac, FL, Florida 33321

Summary

Motivated Engineer, passionate about technologies, software, and healthcare. A multilingual, disciplined, and independent learner with experience in medical sales and customer service. I am willing to work with others, able to learn easily, find quick solutions and work alone effectively.

Skills

- Writing and Communication
- · Logical thinking
- · Self-challenging
- Problem-solving abilities
- · Rapport and relationship building
- Medical knowledge

Education

Bachelor of Science

Universidad Manuela Beltran, Colombia

Biomedical Engineering, 05/2021

Machine Learning Research Project

Universidad Manuela Beltran Pulmonary Nodule Identification On CT Scans, 03/2021

Certificates

- Python
- Data Engineer
- Introduction to Data Science
- C++/C#
- SQL and NoSQL

Experience

SUPMOGO

Medical Sales Engineer 07/2021 to Current

- Increased value to clients through product knowledge, with exceptional research and clinical trial data to support product effectiveness and safety.
- Led team in sales and customer service activities, resolving issues quickly and mentoring new hires.
- Performed data collection for systemizing the client information system.
- Exceeded customer service expectations for clients, leading to increase in repeat business.

CIGNA

Customer Service Representative 12/2020 to 06/2021

- Contact providers, pharmacists and patients regarding home delivery orders and retail claims for medications.
- Promoted high customer satisfaction by resolving problems with knowledgeable and friendly service.
- Answered incoming calls and emails, providing frontline customer support and assistance.
- Demonstrated excellent communication skills in resolving product and consumer complaints.

PHILIPS

Biomedical Engineer Intern 01/2020 to 12/2020

- Medical equipment management procedures such as warranty repairs, end of life-cycle control, maintenance protocols, and legal documentation
- Inventory management for engineering tools, dosimeters, and parts.
- Developed research requirements and prepared documents.

Portfolio

https://milasandovals.github.io/MSandoval_Portfolio/

Languages

English: Spanish: Portuguese: